<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Igniting Coach</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on Igniting Coach</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sergey Podkolzin</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/sergey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/sergey/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My work life, personal relationships and inner wellbeing has improved significantly since I’ve been working with Ilya. He possesses deep, fundamental knowledge and dives deeply into my challenges, offering high-quality and effective techniques. Some of these methods produce immediate results whilst others deliver long-term, high quality impact. Ilya has an attentive, warm presence which greatly enhances my experience. I have worked with many coaches in the past, and he stands out as the best by far.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Dmitriy Chepyzhov</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/dima/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/dima/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Ilya was my guide for my first-ever coaching experience. His combination of professional and personal qualities makes him a true coaching expert. He helped me address several career-related issues, and our work together was crucial in supporting me as I transitioned into my new role and successfully overcame the challenges of adapting to this new chapter in my career.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Maria Em</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/masha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/masha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This was my first coaching experience, and I genuinely enjoyed collaborating with Ilya. His delicate approach allowed us to subtly navigate and address some very important questions. Coaching provided me with a fresh perspective on familiar topics and helped me adjust life strategies that no longer served me well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Divine Machine and the Quest for Peak Performance</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 14:38:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/images/blog/oee.png" alt="Divine machine"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coaching is a way to look at your life from the outside in and unveil key roadblocks that are holding you back from realising your full human potential. Imagine yourself as a perfect divine machine. Let&amp;rsquo;s assume that all your basic needs are satisfied. You have a shelter, food, a partner, and a decent job. Your key resource is your &lt;code&gt;time&lt;/code&gt;. You want to convert this time into things that are important and valuable to you, such as memorable experiences, fulfilling connections, happiness and joy, paintings, music, poetry, money, and so on. What are the opportunities to improve the output of your machine?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>PCI College</title><link>http://localhost:1313/education/pci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/education/pci/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Irish Lifecoach Institute</title><link>http://localhost:1313/education/ili/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/education/ili/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Success</title><link>http://localhost:1313/success/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/success/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;You request has been submitted&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-02/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-02/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I led strategic IT initiatives to transform our global supply chain, significantly improving both operational efficiency and the customer experience. A key part of this work involved implementing an &amp;ldquo;Amazon-like&amp;rdquo; notification system, which successfully reduced customer inquiries by 20%. I also directed the deployment of a new B2B portal, which streamlined the ordering process by pre-filling 60% of fields and cutting the time to order by 23%. My role also included piloting cutting-edge solutions like using Generative AI to optimize SOPs. Additionally, I drove the adoption of the EDI ordering channel, increasing its use to an average of 15% across EMEA, and improved our call response rates by 18% with a new Salesforce-integrated call center. My work on continuous improvements in SAP ECC also reduced non-value-added time for Customer Operations by 30%.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-03/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-03/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;At PwC Ireland, I was a Senior Manager leading complex operational effectiveness projects. A key highlight was directing the Order-to-Cash process rollout for Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Oracle JD Edwards ERP, which included a critical integration with Salesforce. I also spearheaded the implementation of the Camunda Business Process Management system to automate intercompany settlements, which significantly boosted efficiency. My work also involved leading research on the operational impacts of Brexit and contributing to a supply chain risk assessment toolkit for the Irish Food sector.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-01/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As a Senior Manager at PwC Moscow, I focused on strategic and operational projects that delivered tangible results. I specialized in Supply Chain Network Design and ERP implementations, directly saving clients up to $10 million. A key part of my work involved applying Lean Six Sigma principles to improve efficiency. For example, I successfully increased a feed plant&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3% through a SMED project. My experience also includes leading Operational Excellence initiatives across the steel, pharmaceutical, and agribusiness industries.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>St. Petersburg State University</title><link>http://localhost:1313/education/high-school/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/education/high-school/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Footer</title><link>http://localhost:1313/footer/footer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/footer/footer/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Home</title><link>http://localhost:1313/home/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/home/home/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;




&lt;section id="showcase" class="rad-showcase rad-showcase--index rad-animation-group rad-fade-down"&gt;
 &lt;div id="main-content"&gt;
 


 

 &lt;div class="showcase-section row flex-column-reverse flex-md-row rad-fade-down rad-waiting rad-animate"&gt;
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-sm-12 col-md-6 col-lg-6 col-xl-6"&gt;
 &lt;h1 class="display-1"&gt;
 Hello and welcome
 &lt;/h1&gt;
 &lt;h2 class="display-5"&gt;
 &lt;span&gt;&lt;a name='bio'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/h2&gt;
 &lt;div class="lead"&gt;
 &lt;p&gt;It's likely not a coincidence that you've found your way here to Igniting Coach. I'm Ilya Malyarenko, and it's a pleasure to meet you. After spending 15 years as a management consultant and another six in the Biopharma industry, I discovered my true calling: helping others find their way.&lt;p&gt;There's nothing more rewarding to me than mentoring people, guiding them to not only succeed in their careers but also to discover their deeper purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid><description>search</description></item></channel></rss>