<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experience on Igniting Coach</title><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/</link><description>Recent content in Experience on Igniting Coach</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-02/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-02/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I led strategic IT initiatives to transform our global supply chain, significantly improving both operational efficiency and the customer experience. A key part of this work involved implementing an &amp;ldquo;Amazon-like&amp;rdquo; notification system, which successfully reduced customer inquiries by 20%. I also directed the deployment of a new B2B portal, which streamlined the ordering process by pre-filling 60% of fields and cutting the time to order by 23%. My role also included piloting cutting-edge solutions like using Generative AI to optimize SOPs. Additionally, I drove the adoption of the EDI ordering channel, increasing its use to an average of 15% across EMEA, and improved our call response rates by 18% with a new Salesforce-integrated call center. My work on continuous improvements in SAP ECC also reduced non-value-added time for Customer Operations by 30%.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-03/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-03/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;At PwC Ireland, I was a Senior Manager leading complex operational effectiveness projects. A key highlight was directing the Order-to-Cash process rollout for Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Oracle JD Edwards ERP, which included a critical integration with Salesforce. I also spearheaded the implementation of the Camunda Business Process Management system to automate intercompany settlements, which significantly boosted efficiency. My work also involved leading research on the operational impacts of Brexit and contributing to a supply chain risk assessment toolkit for the Irish Food sector.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-01/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As a Senior Manager at PwC Moscow, I focused on strategic and operational projects that delivered tangible results. I specialized in Supply Chain Network Design and ERP implementations, directly saving clients up to $10 million. A key part of my work involved applying Lean Six Sigma principles to improve efficiency. For example, I successfully increased a feed plant&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3% through a SMED project. My experience also includes leading Operational Excellence initiatives across the steel, pharmaceutical, and agribusiness industries.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>