<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Testimonials on Igniting Coach</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/</link><description>Recent content in Testimonials on Igniting Coach</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/testimonial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sergey Podkolzin</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/sergey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/sergey/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My work life, personal relationships and inner wellbeing has improved significantly since I’ve been working with Ilya. He possesses deep, fundamental knowledge and dives deeply into my challenges, offering high-quality and effective techniques. Some of these methods produce immediate results whilst others deliver long-term, high quality impact. Ilya has an attentive, warm presence which greatly enhances my experience. I have worked with many coaches in the past, and he stands out as the best by far.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Dmitriy Chepyzhov</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/dima/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/dima/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Ilya was my guide for my first-ever coaching experience. His combination of professional and personal qualities makes him a true coaching expert. He helped me address several career-related issues, and our work together was crucial in supporting me as I transitioned into my new role and successfully overcame the challenges of adapting to this new chapter in my career.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Maria Em</title><link>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/masha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonial/masha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This was my first coaching experience, and I genuinely enjoyed collaborating with Ilya. His delicate approach allowed us to subtly navigate and address some very important questions. Coaching provided me with a fresh perspective on familiar topics and helped me adjust life strategies that no longer served me well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>